Guide to the Jonathan Edwards Collection
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Edwards Family Correspondence, 1715-1908; Series V; 1.25; (3 boxes)
  - EDWARDS, JONATHAN WALTER
    - Incoming Letters
      - Proudfit, Alexander to [Jonathan W. Edwards?], 1801 May 14 (Box 27, Folder 1516)
      - Rotch, Thomas, 1816 Jun 10 (Box 27, Folder 1517)
      - Ryland, John, 1807 Aug 31 (Box 27, Folder 1518)
      - Tallmadge, Benjamin, 1819 Feb 15 (Box 27, Folder 1519)
  - OTHER CORRESPONDENTS
    - Bellamy, Joseph from
      - Brainerd, David [copy], 1742 Feb 2 (Box 28, Folder 1530)
      - Church of Christ, White Haven, 1768 Dec 20 (Box 28, Folder 1531)
      - Cummings, A., 1763 Apr 16 (Box 28, Folder 1532)
      - Finley, Samuel, 1744 Oct 28 (Box 28, Folder 1533)
      - Foxcroft, Thomas, 1759 (Box 28, Folder 1534)
      - Hawley, Gideon, 1755 Apr 18 (Box 28, Folder 1535)
      - Hopkins, Samuel [copy in an unidentified hand], 1776 Jul 7 (Box 28, Folder 1536)
        With: copies of letters to Jonathan Edwards from Thomas Chapin, 1748 Jun 29, and Chester Williams, 1747 Mar 26
      - Rodgers, John, 1751 Aug 3 (Box 28, Folder 1537)
      - Sherman, Roger, 1772 Jul 23 (Box 28, Folder 1538)
      - Unidentified, cover only, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 1539)
    - Billings, Mr. and Mrs. Charles to Dea. Edwards, Miss Edwards and Marilla Clapp, wedding invitation, 1831 Oct 26 (Box 28, Folder 1540)
    - Burr, Theodosia Bartow (Prevost) to Tapping Reeve, 1788 Mar 12 (Box 28, Folder 1541)
    - Davies, Samuel to [William?] McCullock, 1758 Mar 21 (Box 28, Folder 1542)
    - Dodd, Stephen to Tryon Edwards, 1848 Oct 16 (Box 28, Folder 1543)
    - Edwards, Anne from a nephew, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 1544)
    - Edwards, Bela Bates to Mary H. Cornelius, 1830-47 (Box 28, Folder 1545)
    - Edwards, Edward to his uncle, 1801 Mar 18 (Box 28, Folder 1546)
    - Edwards, Eliza
      - Decorated copies of letters to Abby Tryon and Sally Turner with two related pieces, 1789 (Box 28, Folder 1547)
      - Unsigned invitation from Miss H. S. Saltonstall, and an unsigned acrostic poem (Box 28, Folder 1548)
    - Edwards, Jonathan, 1798-1875
      - To Moses Tryon, 1830 Mar 11 (Box 28, Folder 1549)
      - Invitation, in an unidentified hand, 1835 Dec 23 (Box 28, Folder 1550)
    - Edwards, Timothy, 1669-1758
      - To "Gent[lemen], Brethren, & Christian Friends," draft[?], concerning salary, 1715 Oct (Box 28, Folder 1551)
      - To [William Metcalfe and Abigail Edwards Metcalfe], portion missing, 1745 Jul 11 (Box 28, Folder 1552)
    - Edwards, Timothy, 1738-1813
      - To his wife, 1768 Jan 18 (Box 28, Folder 1553)
      - To an unidentified recipient, fragment, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 1554)
    - Edwards, Walter
      - To Jonathan Edwards, 1822 Jan 31 (Box 28, Folder 1555)
      - To J. E. Hoyt, 1830 Dec 11 (Box 28, Folder 1556)
    - Hawley, Joseph to David Hall, fragment, 1760 May 3 (Box 28, Folder 1557)
    - Hollingsworth, Nancy to her daughter, 1857 Feb 20 (Box 28, Folder 1558)
    - Hollingsworth, Robert to H. M. Lazelle, 1908 Jan 12 (Box 28, Folder 1559)
    - Hopkins, Samuel to "Miss Susa", 1772 Jun 30 (Box 28, Folder 1560)
    - [Hoyt, Mary Edwards?] to John Ryland, draft, incomplete, ca. 1801 (Box 28, Folder 1561)
    - Law, Samuel Andrew
      - To Moses Tryon, 1818 (Box 28, Folder 1562)
        Incl: copy of a letter from Law to Peter Hitchcock, and copies of letters from Law to James McFarlane and Daniel Sheffey with copies of answers from both
      - To Moses Tryon, 1819, 1820 (Box 28, Folder 1563)
      - To Thomas Tryon, 1821 Sep 22 (Box 28, Folder 1564)
    - Lyman, Joseph to Lucy Wetmore, 1768 Oct 5 (Box 28, Folder 1565)
    - Parsons, Jonathan to Jerusha Edwards, 1729 Dec 10 (Box 28, Folder 1566)
    - Pulsifer, David to Alexander B. Grosart, 1854 Jun 17 (Box 28, Folder 1567)
    - Rockwell, Matthew to Jerusha Edwards, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 1568)
    - Stoddard, Esther Warham Mather to Timothy Edwards, 173[6?] Nov 3 (Box 28, Folder 1569)
    - Storrs, Sarah to her parents, Mr. and Mrs. Noah Williston, 1797 Apr 1 (Box 28, Folder 1570)
    - Tryon, Eliza
      See: Eliza Edwards, Box 28, folder 1547
    - Tryon, Moses to Asa Otis, 1818 Jan 4 (Box 28, Folder 1571)
    - Turner, John to Moses Tryon, 1780 Jul 5 (Box 28, Folder 1572)
    - Whittelsey, Chauncey
      - To Lucy Whittelsey, 1790 Jul 27 (Box 28, Folder 1573)
      - To Elizabeth Whittelsey, 1805, 1812 (Box 28, Folder 1574)
      - To Printers, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 1575)
    - Whittelsey, Lucy Wetmore
      - To "my Dear Children", 1785 Jul 18 (Box 28, Folder 1576)
      - To Elizabeth Whittelsey, 1822 Jan 22 (Box 28, Folder 1577)
      - Draft, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 1578)
      - To Chauncey Whittelsey, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 1579)
    - Worrell, Edward to Mrs. Edwards, 1854 Dec 9 (Box 28, Folder 1580)
    - Unidentified
      - Fragment, 1741/2 Feb 3 (Box 28, Folder 1581)
      - Incomplete[?], 1769 Apr 6 (Box 28, Folder 1582)
      - "Dear Madam", 1769 Dec 3 (Box 28, Folder 1583)
      - "To the Printer", n.d. (Box 28, Folder 1584)
  - WETMORE, HANNAH EDWARDS
    - Outgoing Letters
      - Edwards, Esther, 1746, 1760 (Box 28, Folder 1520)
      - Parsons, Jonathan, ca. 1729/30
        See: Oversize, Box 38, folder 1677
      - "Sister", n.d. (Box 28, Folder 1521)
      - Unidentified, two drafts of a letter on the rights of a wife, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 1522)
    - Incoming Letters
      - Edwards, Timothy, 1669-1758, 1750/1 Mar 8 (Box 28, Folder 1523)
      - Hopkins, Esther Edwards, ca. 1736 (Box 28, Folder 1524)
      - Hopkins, Samuel, 1735/6, 1738/9 (Box 28, Folder 1525)
      - Metcalfe, Abigail Edwards, 1737, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 1526)
        With letter from William Metcalfe on verso of 1737 letter
      - Parsons, Jonathan, 1729/30, 1730 (Box 28, Folder 1527)
      - Sargeant, John, 1735-37 (Box 28, Folder 1528)
      - Wetmore, Lucy, 1768 May 11 (Box 28, Folder 1529)
- Genealogical Notes and Other Family Papers, 1696-1891; Series VI; 0.4; (1 box)
  In series VI, Genealogical Notes and Other Family Papers, genealogical notes and information on the Edwards family and related families are placed at the beginning of the series. The section of Other Family Papers is arranged alphabetically by author of subject of the documents.
  - GENEALOGICAL NOTES AND INFORMATION
    - Descendants of Jonathan Edwards, in an unidentified hand, [1874?] (Box 29, Folder 1585)
    - "Family and Descendants of President Jonathan Edwards," printed, annotated, 1891 (Box 29, Folder 1586)
    - Pierpont and Frances Edwards (Box 29, Folder 1587)
    - Notes on leaves from a Bible, in the hand of Tryon Edwards, with related newspaper clippings attached, 1850-84 (Box 29, Folder 1588)
    - Hollingsworth family, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 1589)
    - Daniel Hughes of Ireland (Box 29, Folder 1590)
    - Whittelsey family, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 1591)
  - OTHER FAMILY PAPERS
    - Billings, Charles E. and Sally Storrs: Marriage banns, written and signed by David Childs, town clerk, Conway, 1818 Oct 31 (Box 29, Folder 1592)
    - Dwight, Sereno Edwards: Copy of Jonathan Edwards' "Miscellanies," Book 5, entry 1062, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 1593)
    - Edwards, Bela Bates: Greek alphabet and declensions (Box 29, Folder 1594)
    - Edwards, Elisha: Direction to Phineas Strong to pay certain sums to six people, Southampton, 1803 Sep 5 (Box 29, Folder 1595)
    - Edwards, Jonathan, 1745-1801
      - Indenture, draft, for land in New York, 1795 Sep 18
        See: Oversize, Box 38, folder 1678
      - Prayer, in Mahican, 1765 May 27 (Box 29, Folder 1596)
      - Will, 1785 Sep 6 (Box 29, Folder 1597)
    - Edwards, Jonathan Walter, 1772-1881
      - Certificate of admission to the bar of Connecticut, manuscript, 1798 Sep 18 (Box 29, Folder 1598)
      - Deed to a lot in the North Burying Ground in Hartford, printed, completed in manuscript, 1813 Jan 9 (Box 29, Folder 1599)
      - Exemplification of proofs, etc. in the matter of the will of JWE, deceased, 1831 Sep 21 (Box 29, Folder 1600)
    - Edwards, Timothy, 1738-1813
      - "Cession of New York to Massachusetts of Western Lands", 1786 (Box 29, Folder 1601)
      - "Drought of Chenango Township", n.d. (Box 29, Folder 1602)
      - "List of Deeds belonging to Rev'd Jonathan Edwards", 1787 Sep 20 (Box 29, Folder 1603)
    - Eels, Nathaniel: "Their Church Covenant. Church Articles of Faith, and Body of Principles", 1768 Apr (Box 29, Folder 1604)
    - Kennedy, Lydia Eliza Hollingsworth: bound album of manuscript poems and printed illustrations, 1840 (Box 29, Folder 1605)
      Inscribed: "Presented to his daughter /from her affectionate father/Jacob Hollingsworth/April 1840
    - Treadwell, H. E.: Edwards family epitaphs from the East Windsor Hill graveyard, 1832 May (Box 29, Folder 1606)
    - Trustees of the College of New Jersey: copy, in an unidentified hand, of the Latin inscription placed by the Trustees on Jonathan Edwards' tomb (Box 29, Folder 1607)
    - Tryon, Moses: list of the crew of a vessel commanded by Moses Tryon (Box 29, Folder 1608)
    - Turner, John: announcement that John Turner and Elisabeth Haynes intend to wed (Box 29, Folder 1609)
    - Ware, John
      Related Materials
      See: Ware, John: appointment as lieutenant of foot company in Wrentham, Massachusetts, Box 38, folder 1678a
    - [empty folder], 1696 Aug 5 (Box 29, Folder 1610)
    - Ware, Nathaniel
      - Indenture for Pero Gardiner to be apprenticed to Nathaniel Ware, printed, completed in manuscript, 1792 Jan 6 (Box 29, Folder 1611)
      - Indenture for Pero Gardiner, witnessed and signed by Warren and Nabby Ware, 1793 Feb 12 (Box 29, Folder 1612)
      - Appointment as captain of second company of militia in Wrentham, Massachusetts, printed, completed in manuscript, 1746 May 23
        See: Oversize, Box 38, folder 1679
    - Williams, Ephraim, 1714-1755: copy of his will of 1755 Jul 22, 1878 Jun 26 (Box 29, Folder 1613)
    - Winthrop, John: manuscript copy, in an unknown hand of extracts from "Farewell to the Church of England" (Box 29, Folder 1614)
    - Unidentified: direction to Samuel Edwards, treasurer, to pay certain sums to twelve people, Southampton, signed by Aaron Clark and Elias Lyman, 1768 Apr 12 (Box 29, Folder 1615)
- Printed Material, 1758-1959; Series VII; 1.75; (4 boxes)
  Series VII, Printed Material, is arranged alphabetically by title when known, or type of material, with family Bibles and other volumes listed at the end of the series in storage order.
  - "The Daily Life of the Christian Child," Hagerstown: Bell & Marsh, 1850 (Box 30, Folder 1616)
  - Ephemera removed from family Bibles, 1893-1903, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 1617)
  - "Hollingsworth Genealogical Memoranda in the United States from 1682 to 1884," by William B. Hollingsworth, printed by him in Baltimore (Box 30, Folder 1618)
  - "Jonathan Edwards: An Address delivered in Utica, N.Y. on the 200th Anniversary of his birth, October 5th, 1903.," by G. H. Humphrey (Box 30, Folder 1619)
  - "The Manuscripts of Jonathan Edwards," by Franklin Bowditch Dexter, Cambridge: John Wilson and Son, 1901 (Box 30, Folder 1620)
  - Letter to the editors of the N. E. Puritan by Timothy Edwards, clipping, 1843 Nov
    See: Oversize, Box 38, folder 1680
  - Letter to the editors of the N. E. Puritan by Joseph H. Bellamy, concerning Aaron Burr, clipping, 1848 Oct 9
    See: Oversize, Box 38, folder 1681
  - Newspaper clippings about the Hollingsworth family, 1848-1920 (Box 30, Folder 1621)
  - Newspaper clippings, mainly concerning the Bible, religion, 1834-52, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 1622)
  - Newspaper clippings of birth, wedding, and death announcements, 1843-1959, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 1623)
  - Thanksgiving proclamation by George Washington, New York, 1789 Oct 3
    See: Oversize, Box 38, folder 1682
  - Thanksgiving proclamation by Samuel Huntington, New Haven, 1792 Oct 24
    See: Oversize, Box 38, folder 1683
  - Obituary of Jonathan Edwards, newspaper clipping, 1758 Apr 10 (Box 30, Folder 1624)
  - Book of Common Prayer, New York: White, Gallagher, & White, 1828 (Box 31, Folder 1625)
    Inscribed: "William H. Stokes/Yale College/Jan 1831"
  - Book of Common Prayer, London (Box 31, Folder 1626)
    Inscribed: "Lilly H. Kennedy/ Christmas 1872" and "Tryon H. Edwards/March 19, 1882/Hagerstown, Maryland, with obituaries and photograph pasted in
  - Daily Food for Christians, Portland: Sanborn & Carter, 1851 (Box 31, Folder 1627)
    Inscribed: "To Tryon Edwards Jr./A New Year's Memento/from his Teacher/ Jan. 1 '54"
  - Le Nouveau Testament, London: Société pour l'impression de la Bible en langue anglaise et en langues étrangères, 1860 (Box 31, Folder 1628)
    Inscribed: Tryon H. Edwards/from his Aunt/Maria C. Edwards/Troy, Sept. 8, 1863" and Lydia H. K. Edwards/9 November 1887/Hagerstown/Maryland"
  - Holy Bible, New York: American Bible Society, 1860 (Box 31, Folder 1629)
    Inscribed: "Lillie H. Kennedy/from/ Annie T. Blow/June 25th 1861." With: obituaries pasted in
  - Holy Bible. Hartford: Hudson & Co., 1816 (Box 32, Folder 1630)
    With: several Tryon Edwards signatures and dates, 1817-50, poems and quotations pasted and written in
  - Holy Bible, Edinburgh, 1821 (Box 32, Folder 1631)
    Inscribed: "To/James H. Kennedy/from his affectionate father/May 10th 1825"
  - Holy Bible, Baltimore: Armstrong and Berry, 1839 (Box 32, Folder 1632)
    Inscribed: "Lillie H. Kennedy/her dear mother's bible/June [18]56"
  - Holy Bible. New York: American Bible Society, 1867 (Box 32, Folder 1633)
    Inscribed: "Lillie H. Kennedy/from/ Brother & Sister/Christmas 1867" and "Mrs. T. H. Edwards/Hagerstown Md." and "Lydia Hollingsworth Kennedy Edwards"
  - Holy Bible, New York: American Bible Society, 1890 (Box 32, Folder 1634)
    Inscribed:"To Lydia H. Edwards/from her loving grandfather/T.E./Jan. 3, 1891"
  - Holy Bible, missing title page, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 1635)
  - Light for the Day; or, Heavenly Thoughts for Earthly Guidance, by Tryon Edwards, Philadephia: Presbyterian Board of Publication, 1877 (Box 32, Folder 1636)
    Inscribed: "T. H. Edwards/from his father/1880," with pamphlet pasted in: No Sect in Heaven. New York: Warren & Wyman
  - Holy Bible. Philadelphia: Mathew Carey, 1810 (Box 33, Folder 1637)
    With: obituaries pasted in and manuscript notes of Hollingsworth family births and deaths
- Visual Material, 1783-1908; Series VIII; 0.2; (1 box)
  Series VII, Visual Material, contains photographs, engravings, and silhouettes and is arranged alphabetically by subject matter. Unidentified photographs are placed at the end of the series.
  - Edwards, Eugene
    - Photograph, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 1638)
    - Daguerreotype, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 1639)
  - Edwards, Jonathan
    - Print, engraving, cut from Timothy Alden's A Collection of American Epitaphs, with engraving of [Sarah Pierpont Edwards?], 1815, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 1640)
    - Prints, engravings of portraits, 1783-97, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 1641)
  - Edwards, Martha Ellen (Phelps)
    - Photographs, two, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 1642)
    - Daguerreotype, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 1643)
  - Edwards, Pierpont: engraving by Max Rosenthal, four copies, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 1644)
  - Edwards, Timothy: photograph of manuscript sermons by Timothy Edwards, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 1645)
  - Edwards crest, embossed, and Edwards arms, printed and sketched (Box 34, Folder 1646)
  - Hollingsworth family: photographic postcards of Lucille H. Hollingsworth, Sallie-Belle Hollingsworth, and Robert, Ruth, and Laverne Hollingsworth, 1908 (Box 34, Folder 1647)
  - Hooker, Asahel: cut-out silhouette, with silhouette of an unidentified woman, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 1648)
  - Pierpont, James: photograph taken from a print of an oil portrait, 1886 Feb 3 (Box 34, Folder 1649)
  - Pierpont, Mary: photograph taken from a print of an oil portrait, [1886?] (Box 34, Folder 1650)
  - Trumbull family: four silhouettes on single sheet, of Governor Trumbull, Colonel Trumbull, Mrs. Trumbull, and Miss Alsop (Box 34, Folder 1651)
  - Unidentified photographs, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 1652)
- Artifacts, n.d.; Series IX; 1.75; (2 boxes)
  Series IX, Artifacts, is arranged alphabetically by type of material.
  - Binder (Box 35, Folder 1653)
  - Binder (Box 35, Folder 1654)
  - Fragment of the wedding dress of Sarah Pierpont Edwards, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1655)
  - Linen bedsheet with embroidered initials, made by Esther Stoddard Edwards, accompanied by 19th century note about the sheet, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 1656)
- History of the Papers, 1767-1972; Series X; 0.2; (1 box)
  Series X, History of the Papers, is organized in two subseries, Correspondence, arranged alphabetically by correspondent, and Agreements, Inventories, and Related Papers, arranged alphabetically by title or type of material.
  - CORRESPONDENCE
    - Allen, Alexander V. G. to Franklin B. Dexter, with copy of letter from Tryon Edwards, 1904 Sep 6 (Box 37, Folder 1657)
    - Dwight, Timothy to Tryon Edwards, 1890 Oct 23 (Box 37, Folder 1658)
    - Edwards, Tryon to various recipients, 1884-93 (Box 37, Folder 1659)
    - Ferris, Francis Marion to Tryon Edwards, 1893 Mar 29 (Box 37, Folder 1660)
    - Park, Agnes to Addison Van Name, 1900 Aug 2 (Box 37, Folder 1661)
    - Park, Edwards A. to Eli Whitney, Jr., 1895 Feb 16 (Box 37, Folder 1662)
    - Smythe, Egbert C. to Franklin G. Dexter, 1874 May 23 (Box 37, Folder 1663)
    - Whitney, Eli, Jr. from various Edwards heirs, 1890-98 (Box 37, Folder 1664)
    - Woodbridge, Mrs. Timothy to Professor Thacher, 1870 Jan 6 (Box 37, Folder 1665)
  - AGREEMENTS, INVENTORIES, AND RELATED PAPERS
    - Agreement, assigning possession of Edwards manuscripts to Jonathan Edwards, signed by his seven of his siblings, 1767 Mar 27 (Box 37, Folder 1666)
    - Agreement, arranging for deposit of Edwards manuscripts at Yale, signed by the great grandchildren of Jonathan Edwards, 1890 Oct 7 (Box 37, Folder 1667)
    - "Edwardean," inventory of the Edwards manuscripts and notes on Edwards by William Edwards Park, manuscript, in bound volume (Box 37, Folder 1668)
      With 1935 letter about the volume
    - "Hard Hearted Hannah," paper written for the Monday Evening Club of Hartford by John De K. Alsop, about the Hannah Edwards Wetmore correspondence, 1972 Jan 3 (Box 37, Folder 1669)
    - Index to the Jonathan Edwards manuscripts, prepared by W. J. B. Edgar, 1935, typescript, with 1964 amended copy, typescript, 1935, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 1670)
    - Inventory, compiled by L. F. Partridge, Professor Park's secretary, that accompanied manuscripts when they arrived at Yale University Library, [1900?] (Box 37, Folder 1671)
    - Inventory, compiled by L. F. Partridge, titled: "Hurried Copy of Contents of Box of Mss. sent to Yale," with an early 19th century leaf headed: "Most important, Edwards Papers", n.d. (Box 37, Folder 1672)
    - List of Edwards manuscripts, in the hand of Tryon Edwards, numbered 1 to 45 (Box 37, Folder 1673)
    - List of Edwards manuscripts and letters, in the hand of Tryon Edwards, with the notation "Sent by mail to Prof. Park. Mch 14. 71," incomplete, items are numbered 17 to 30 (Box 37, Folder 1674)
    - Lists of the great grandchildren of Jonathan Edwards, notebook and single leaf, 1892, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 1675)
    - Transcriptions by F. B. Dexter[?] and William P. Upham of the notes on the cover of "Notes on Natural Science," with related material, 1901-02, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 1676)
- Oversize, 2; (1 box)
  Box 38 contains oversize material from Series V, VI, and VII, in series order.
  - EDWARDS FAMILY CORRESPONDENCE
    - Wetmore, Hannah Edwards to Jonathan Parsons, ca. 1729/30 (Box 38, Folder 1677)
  - GENEALOGICAL NOTES AND OTHER FAMILY PAPERS
    - Edwards, Jonathan, 1745-1801: indenture, draft, for land in New York, 1795 Sep 18 (Box 38, Folder 1678)
    - Ware, John: appointment as lieutenant of foot company in Wrentham, Massachusetts, printed, completed in manuscript, with manuscript notes on verso, 1696 August 5 (Box 38, Folder 1678a)
    - Ware, Nathaniel: Appointment as captain of second company of militia in Wrentham, Massachusetts, 1746 May 23 (Box 38, Folder 1679)
  - PRINTED MATERIAL
    - Letter to the editors of the N. E. Puritan by Timothy Edwards, clipping, 1843 Nov (Box 38, Folder 1680)
    - Letter to the editors of the N. E. Puritan by Joseph H. Bellamy, clipping, 1848 Oct 9 (Box 38, Folder 1681)
    - Thanksgiving proclamation by George Washington, New York, 1789 Oct 3 (Box 38, Folder 1682)
    - Thanksgiving proclamation by Samuel Huntington, New Haven, 1792 Oct 24 (Box 38, Folder 1683)